indochino.com 2019-12-31

# INDOCHINO | Men's Custom Suits

Last updated: November 1, 2019

Indochino Apparel Inc. ("Indochino") is committed to protecting the privacy rights of our customers and visitors to our showrooms and website, [www.indochino.com](http://www.indochino.com/). Indochino knows that you care how information about you is collected, used and shared, and we appreciate your trust.

By providing us with personal information, visiting our showrooms, or accessing, browsing or otherwise using this Website, you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this privacy policy.

## WHO WE ARE

Indochino is the pioneer and global leader in online custom suits. With an innovative approach, not only do we provide stylish suits in fine fabrics at the best price with the fastest delivery time, we are revolutionizing the way men dress. Read reviews from the customers who love us and learn why Indochino makes the finest custom suits.

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience. We collect personal information from you when you voluntarily provide it to us. We also collect certain information automatically when you visit our website or our showrooms. We will also at times collect personal information from third parties.

View our cookie policy

## INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE

During your use of Indochino.com, such as registering for My Account and signing into your account, you will be asked to provide personal information (such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, credit card information, measurement details, etc.) for the purpose of facilitating communications with you or facilitating your use of Indochino.com, including placing an order for custom made apparel, backing up your measurements online, signing up to receive the latest product releases, style advice, fashion tips, using the Refer a Friend feature, purchasing a Gift Certificate and receiving promotion codes. We will also collect similar information from you when you visit our showrooms. If you choose not to provide certain requested personal information, you will not be able to register as an Indochino customer, obtain certain products or services, or use certain features of the Website.

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT AUTOMATICALLY

Indochino.com uses "cookies", a technology that stores a small amount of information on a website user's computer to permit the website to recognize future visits using that computer. Cookies enhance the convenience and use of Indochino.com. For example, the information provided through cookies is used to recognize you as a previous user (so you do not have to enter your personal information every time), offer personalized web page content and information for your use and otherwise facilitate your website experience. Cookie data may be used for purposes including delivering to you banner advertisements and other advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain websites and selecting offers and products to display to you when you visit our website. You may also wish to decline cookies generally if your browser permits, but doing so may affect your use of the website.

We use this profiling to manage and tailor the content and services we provide to you.

To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mails from Indochino.com if your computer supports such capabilities. If you do not wish to receive e-mail or other mail from Indochino, please simply click unsubscribe.

Information is also automatically collected from your mobile device (if Wi-Fi is enabled) when you visit our showrooms. We collect this information from our third party partner, as described in more detail in the Information We Collect From Third Parties section below.

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM THIRD PARTIES

We will also collect personal information from friends or family members who have referred you to us, for example, in connection with a Refer-A-Friend promotion.

## HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We use the information that we collect about you to:

  * Process and fulfill your orders and provide customer service.
  * Manage your Account.
  * Administer the Website.
  * Monitor customer online and offline traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop and improve the design and usability of the site, our showrooms, our products and services and our marketing campaigns.
  * Protect the security or integrity of our website and our business.
  * Notify you about enhancement to our services, such as recent updates to the Website, new services and special offers that may be of interest.

If you are in the European Economic Area ("EEA"), we will rely on one of the following legal grounds (as appropriate) to process your personal data:

  * To enter and perform a contract with you or to perform any steps you require from us before entering into a contract.
  * To pursue our legitimate business interests in providing you with our products and services.
  * Your specific consent to us using your information, which you can withdraw at any time.
  * To comply with our legal obligations and establish, exercise or defend our legal rights.

## DO WE SHARE THE INFORMATION WE RECEIVE?

We may share personal information as described below.

## DISCLOSURE TO AUTHORIZING PERSONS

If you use the website on behalf of another person or organization (such as your employer), Indochino may provide your personal information to that authorizing person/organization. Indochino has no control over the use of your personal information by the authorizing person/organization, and that use is not subject to this Policy.

## DISCLOSURE TO AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS AND SERVICE PROVIDERS

Indochino will provide your personal information to its affiliated businesses, such as Indochino (Shanghai) Apparel Inc. or other suppliers and service providers as necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy (for example, to provide products or services, advertising and marketing, for data analysis, to enhance the information collected from or about you and for payment processing and shipping, etc). Indochino requires its affiliated businesses, suppliers and service providers to agree to use your personal information only for the purposes for which it is provided to them, and to protect the privacy of your personal information in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. Some of these affiliates, suppliers and service providers may be located outside of Canada, including in the United States, the United Kingdom and China.

## DISCLOSURE IN BUSINESS TRANSFERS

Indochino may be involved in the sale or transfer of some or all of its business. As part of that sale or transfer, Indochino may disclose your personal information to the acquiring organization, but will require the acquiring organization to agree to protect the privacy of your personal information in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. Indochino has no liability for the acquiring organization's use and disclosure of your personal information.

## LAW ENFORCEMENT AND LEGAL DISCLOSURE

Indochino (or its affiliates, suppliers and service providers) may disclose your personal information to a Canadian or foreign government institution or regulatory authority that has asserted its lawful authority to obtain the information, but in each case only where Indochino has reasonable grounds to believe the information could be useful in the investigation of unlawful activity, or to comply with a subpoena or warrant or an order made by a court, person or body with jurisdiction to compel the production of information, or to comply with court rules regarding the production of records and information, or to its legal counsel, or as otherwise might be required in compliance with applicable data protection legislation.

## WITH YOUR CONSENT

Indochino will disclose your personal information in other circumstances, but only with your consent.

## HOW SECURE IS MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We work to protect the security of your information. For example, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input online during transmission to us. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should change from "http" to "https." We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are using Internet. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

## FOR HOW LONG WILL YOU STORE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?

Personal information is retained in accordance with record retention policies. Our record retention periods are established taking into account requirements of privacy laws, the purposes for which the information was collected, legal and regulatory requirements to retain the information for minimum periods, limitation periods for taking legal action, and our business purposes.

## WHAT OPTIONS DO I HAVE?

You can add or update certain information on pages such as those referenced in the My Account section, simply logging in with your email address and password. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please simply click Unsubscribe button in your email newsletter.

To request access to or correction of your personal information in our custody or control, please contact us as described below. We may take reasonable steps to verify your identity before providing access to or correction of your personal information.

## YOUR RIGHTS

If you are in the EEA and we hold some of your personal information, you have the following rights in respect of that information:

  * To request access to that information.
  * To ask us to update or amend your personal information if it is inaccurate or incomplete.
  * To object to our use of your personal data.
  * To request the deletion of your personal information, or restrict its use.
  * To withdraw any consents you have provided in respect of our use of your information.
  * To request a copy of information you have provided to us, to use for your own purposes.
  * To lodge a complaint with the relevant data protection supervisory authority.

## CHILDREN'S POLICY

Indochino does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information online from individuals under the age of 13. If we have reason to believe that we may have accidentally recieved personal information from an individual under the age of 13, please contact us immediately at [info@indochino.com](mailto:info@indochino.com).

## POLICY UPDATE

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates in this webpage. This privacy policy is effective as of the last updated date above.

## YOUR FEEDBACK

If you have any comments or questions about this Policy or your personal information, please send your comments by e-mail to our Privacy Representative at [info@indochino.com](mailto:info@indochino.com).

## HEADQUARTERS

#300 – 720 Robson Street, Vancouver, BC V6Z 1A1, Canada.
